http://www.keyboardspecialists.co.uk/pages/privacy

X-keys Accessories
KBS understands the value of your privacy especially on the internet. We want you to enjoy your shopping experience with us in the safe knowledge that we take every precaution to ensure your privacy is maintained.
If you have any questions about the handling or protection of your personal detail, or your rights under this Online Agreement or if you would like to unsubscribe from marketing material then please contact us in writing by post at Keyboard Specialists Ltd, Unit 44-45 Darlaston Central Trading Estate, Wednesbury,  West Midlands, WS10 8XB, United Kingdom or email us at info@KeyboardSpecialists.co.uk.
The Information We Collect
The types of personal information we collect or is submitted via our website are:
Your name
Company name
Billing Address
Delivery address
Telephone number
Email address
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that order and provide the service you require. KBS does not disclose or share this information with third parties except to the extent necessary to complete your order. On rare occasions it may be necessary for us to communicate with you for the administrative or operational reasons relating to the services we have provided to you.
Credit/debit card transactions are securely handled by PayPal, SagePay and Shopify Payments. Your details go directly for processing through a secure connection, they are not stored on our site and are not retrievable by us.
We will only share the delivery information you provide about yourself or someone else with reputable distribution institutions such as the Royal Mail and our partner courier companies (DPD, UPS, Business Post, TNT) to delivery your order/s. Please rest assured that those companies and individuals who have access to any such personal information are not permitted to use this information for any other purposes and they are required to process any such data in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.
We use anonymised and aggregate information for statistical purposes to improve the website and the products we offer. However we do not disclose anything that could be used to identify any individuals
Your personal details will remain private and confidential. All data collected is for our internal use only. Any information you provide and store on our website is only accessible by you after you have entered your Username and Password.
We do not sell mailing lists to other companies, or divulge any of your personal details to other companies or individuals.
Data Security
When you place orders or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. For credit card transactions, KBS adds security by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology, with 128 bit encryption. This means that the credit card information you send is encrypted by your computer, and then decrypted again on our side, preventing others from accessing your private information in between. So, when using an SSL capable browser, shopping on the KBS web site is the safest kind of transaction possible with a credit card.
Furthermore, as required by the UK Data Protection Legislation, we follow strict security procedures in the storage and disclosure of information which you have given us, to prevent unauthorised access. Our security procedures mean that we may occasionally request proof of identity before we are able to disclose sensitive information to you. For further information please contact info@KeyboardSpecialists.co.uk.
Communication with You
KBS have an anti-SPAM policy, we will NEVER send you any unsolicited e-mail. If you have opted-in to our free newsletter, you will receive one occasionally. Clear unsubscribe details are always shown on the newsletter.
If you choose not to receive our free newsletter, we will only contact you to answer your queries and/or send you details regarding your order. We will not contact you any other time.
We may from time to time post up surveys to measure your response to certain new additions to the website. As a rule, you are never forced to fill in these surveys. Furthermore, should you choose to fill in the surveys, you can choose to remain anonymous.
What about Cookies?
Cookies are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide a unique session ID as a feature which allows shopping, and to store items in your Shopping Basket between visits. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Even without a cookie, you can still use most of the features in our store, including placing items in your Shopping Basket and purchasing them.
Marketing
If you have used the KBS website before for browsing or purchasing products, it is possible that we may have information about you which is being used to provide information to you regarding offers or events etc that you may find useful. We will continue to provide you with such information unless you request us not to.
If you are a new customer we will ask you whether or not you would like to receive information on future offers, events, new products and related activities which we believe could be useful for you. We assure you that we will not inundate you with meaningless (junk) emails, but would like to keep you up-to-date with what’s going on at KBS.
We do not sell, trade or rent your personal information to other companies.
We agree not to send you any marketing emails or pass your details over to third parties unless you give us your permission to do so by opting in, or unless you have already opted in.
How You Can Access or Correct Your Information
You Can withdraw your consent to processing or access all your personal information that we collect and maintain in writing by post at Keyboard Specialists Ltd, Unit 44-45 Darlaston Central Trading Estate, Wednesbury,  West Midlands, WS10 8XB, United Kingdom or email us at info@KeyboardSpecialists.co.uk.
Help Center
News
Glossary
Customised Keyboards
International Keyboards
About Us
Contact Us
FAQ
Join our periodic newsletter to keep up to date on new technology and special offers
Keyboard Specialists LtdUnit 44-45, Darlaston Central Trading EstateSalisbury StreetWednesburyWest MidlandsWS10 8XBUnited Kingdom
Copyright © 2020 Keyboard Specialists LTD.
Added to your cart:
Subtotal
